

TERESIA SOMERVILLE

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

(+91) 933-092-9083 info@mycvdesigner.com Sydney, Australia

twitter.com/t_somervdummy20

w vk.com/t_somervdummy20

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Senior graphic design professional with 8+ years of experience in Design, art direction and management of print and digital projects from conception through completion. Specialized in creating Book and Cover Design; logo; after effects; Animation and many more by using various adobe suite and graphic design tools.

CORE COMPETENCIES

Typography

Design aptitude

Research and Analytical Skills

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER • May 2017 - Present

Brandcraft, Sydney, Australia

- **BrandCraft**
- Create and design unique visual images, flash presentations, animation and web application interface for various internal and external projects.
- Assign projects to meet department objectives and requirements of various business units & Ensuring department projects are completed on time by coordinating activities.
- Design of banner ads and web graphics for online Travel promotions: photo selection and color correction, copy development and optimization.
- Design Bar charts, Rectangular charts and various types of infographics for the presentation and reporting purposes for client deals.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER • June 2015 - Jan 2017

Chello, Sydney, Australia



- · Responsible for Campaign concepts and ideas including Logo Design and Illustration for all brand strategies and Created design; presentation boards to help support executive and account representation of strategic creative to the client.
- Handle a team of 10 members including 2 freelancers and reporting their progress to the head of the department and solving all the errors.

FREELANCE GRAPHIC DESIGNER • Apr 2012 - Apr 2015

April Ford, Maroochydore, Australia



- Designed multiple Logo; Brochure; Newsletters and Magazines and created 5 short product animation and introductory videos for social media sites for the clients across the globe.
- Designed Static and dynamic images and short animation clips for various online websites.
- Learn & implement subject matters into design for inforgraphics, Newsletters, Company portfolios, training and corporate videos and sales presentations.

EDUCATION & CREDENTIALS

Masters of Fine Arts in Visual Communication • 2011

acquarie University, Sydney, Australia



TECHNICAL SKILLS



Affinity Designer



Procreate



Photoshop

InDesign



Illustrator CC



Corel Painter 2020











PORTFOLIO

www.mycvdesi

